Hakan Gundogdu

Frontend Developer

ري

https://www.hakangundogdu.com

in http://linkedin.com/in/hakangundogdu1

https://github.com/hakangundogdu

(

Izmir, Turkey (GMT+3)

+90-532-621-7091

hakan.gundogdu@gmail.com

Experienced React Developer with 3+ years of experience. Self-motivated person with the ability to work to the highest ethical standards. Adaptive and fast-learner of new technologies and business requirements. Effective communicator with co-workers, able to work both independently and in a diverse global team.

Areas of Expertise

- React
- Typescript
- Javascrit ES6

- Redux
- NextJS
- TailwindCSS

- HTML/CSS
- Finance / Fintech
- Git

Experience

Abilitie, United States, 03/2022 - 05/2022

Software Engineer, https://abilitie.com

• Developed React Career web app for B2B, B2C.

React, TypeScript, Javascript, Material UI, Tailwind CSS, Styled Components, GraphQL, Git

Freelance, Worlwide, 01/2019 - Now

Software Engineer, Top-Rated-Plus Freelancer (Upwork)

- Designed and developed engaging webpages and web applications.
- Designed Pitch Decks and other marketing documents.
- Some of my 200 clients: Johnson & Johnson, Novartis, Estee Lauder, Glasswall, Protective

React, Next JS, TypeScript, Tailwind, HTML, CSS, WordPress, Git, Jira, Figma, Adobe Software

Trounceflow, London, UK, 04/2019 - 08/2019

Developer / Analyst, https://wp.trounceflow.com

- Managed frontend of the product
- Analysed financial data and created reports and insights.

Javascript, HTML, CSS

Other Experiences

Bayyurt Group, Financial Analyst, Turkey, 2018 – 2019

Turkish Treasury, Senior Associate, Advisor to Head of Treasury, Turkey, 2008 - 2016

Education

BA, Bogazici University, Economics, 2007, Istanbul, Turkey